[GREMLINS CHITTERING ON TV]
(Sheldon:)This movie baffles me
every time we watch it.
(Leonard:)What do you mean?
(Sheldon:)The instructions are very clear.
Don't feed the gremlins after midnight.
(Sheldon:)Don't get the gremlins wet.
(Sheldon:)How hard is that?
(Penny(arriving):)Hi, guys.
(Penny(arriving):)-Hi, honey.
-Hey.
Oh, we're "honey" now, are we?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Since their relationship
became carnal...
(Sheldon:)...Penny has upgraded
his designated term of endearment...
(Sheldon:)...distinguishing him
from those she calls "sweetie"...
(Sheldon:)...in an attempt to soften
a thinly veiled insult.
(Penny:)You're boring people, sweetie.
(Sheldon:)Although sometimes
she omits the veil entirely.
(Penny:)-So, what are you guys doing?
-Celebrating Columbus Day.
(Leonard:)We're watching Goonies, Gremlins
and Young Sherlock Holmes.
They're all written by Chris Columbus.
(Penny:)Okay. What do you watch
on Thanksgiving?